<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Audio on Wish&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/tags/audio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Audio on Wish&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wish2333.github.io/en/tags/audio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Webclass-AutoCut based on Free Software</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/webclass-autocut-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/webclass-autocut-free/</guid>
      <description>Application Scenarios Online Course Editing: Legacy Courses: Batch update of intros and outros across varied formats (encoding, resolution, frame rate, audio format). New Course Recordings: Processing raw files, focusing on noise reduction, removal of blank segments, and adding standardized intros and outros. Rapid Slicing &amp;amp; Content Review: Based on scripts, for swift editing and review, crucial for content flagged for modification. Requirements Breakdown Legacy Courses: Objective: Replace (delete + add),</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio Drama Script Based on Kazuha</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2021/radio-drama-script-base-kazuha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2021/radio-drama-script-base-kazuha/</guid>
      <description>Seagulls silent, traveler&amp;rsquo;s sentiment; red leaves aflame, heart of benevolence and righteousness. Setting Disclaimer: This is a derivative creation, all copyrights belong to miHoYo.&#xA;All plot elements are purely fictional and unrelated to any historical figures or nations.&#xA;Introduction In a time of extreme instability across the globe, the General suddenly issued a Sword Hunt Decree, ordering the confiscation of swords carried by civilians, which incited discontent among various samurai factions and civilian organizations, leading them to unite and form a resistance army.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
