<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Article on Wish&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://wish2333.github.io/tags/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Article on Wish&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wish2333.github.io/tags/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Practice Paths for Cultural Square Empowerment in Rural Revitalization Under the Context of Cultural and Tourism Communication--An Investigation Based on Feng Village, a National Key Rural Tourism Site in Guangxi, China</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/2024/tourism-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/2024/tourism-communication/</guid>
      <description>This article is entirely my original work, completed independently on January 10, 2024. Kindly respect the intellectual property rights. The full Chinese text, appendices, reference citations, and other related content are available in the accompanying PDF document. tourism_communication.pdf Abstract With the proposition of rural revitalization and the rise of cultural and tourism industries, the demand for rural image construction and dissemination has increasingly become prominent. Rural cultural squares, as essential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Spatial Inequality within The Dingfuzhuang Community</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/2023/social-spatial-inequality-within-dingfuzhuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/2023/social-spatial-inequality-within-dingfuzhuang/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Through an urban sociological lens, this investigation will delve deeply into the unequal distribution and utilization of social spaces among different areas, neighborhoods, or specific locales within the Dingfuzhuang area of Chaoyang District, Beijing. We aim to identify the concrete manifestations of such inequalities within the particular community, encompassing aspects such as the distribution of infrastructure, allocation of public service facilities, and usage patterns of residential public spaces. Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Process of Research in Dingfuzhuang Community</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/2023/the-creative-process-of-dingfuzhuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/2023/the-creative-process-of-dingfuzhuang/</guid>
      <description>理解城市-结课作业 2023-10-28选题：黄淼森 社会空间不平等问题 参考文献 https://zhuanlan.zhihu.com/p/452072791 https://zhuanlan.zhihu.com/p/106501422 https://www.sohu.com/a/482049556_121124003 http://fjyl.cnjournals.com/fjyl/ch/reader/create_pdf.aspx?file_no=20200910&amp;amp;flag=1&amp;amp;journal_id=fjyl&amp;amp;year_id=2020 https://book.douban.com/review/14200117/ 选题报告 在报告中，将关注的主题定为“身边的社区存在的社</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study on the Adoption of Health Information by College Students in Beijing on User-Generated Content Platforms--A Case of Xiaohongshu</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/2023/health-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/2023/health-information/</guid>
      <description>The present article represents a collaborative effort completed by five co-authors, with my contribution focusing specifically on the literature review and data processing sections. The text below encompasses the content of those segments, while the comprehensive full-text version is attached as a PDF file for your reference. ！Download Full Text Abstract This study focuses on the contemporary representative Internet new media platform</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cold and Warmth of the Police Station</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/2022/the-cold-and-warmth-of-the-police-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/2022/the-cold-and-warmth-of-the-police-station/</guid>
      <description>Introduction On March 11th, the documentary Guarding Liberation West 3, co-produced by the Changsha Public Security Bureau and Bilibili, came to a successful conclusion, amassing over 200 million views and sparking heated discussions. Throughout the series, it featured both bizarre incidents that left viewers laughing and crying, as well as thrilling on-site arrests, showcasing both the stern and rigorous law enforcement procedures and heartwarming grassroots services. Behind the hustle and</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
