<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Media Literacy on Wish&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://wish2333.github.io/tags/media-literacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Media Literacy on Wish&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wish2333.github.io/tags/media-literacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Practice Paths for Cultural Square Empowerment in Rural Revitalization Under the Context of Cultural and Tourism Communication--An Investigation Based on Feng Village, a National Key Rural Tourism Site in Guangxi, China</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/2024/tourism-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/2024/tourism-communication/</guid>
      <description>This article is entirely my original work, completed independently on January 10, 2024. Kindly respect the intellectual property rights. The full Chinese text, appendices, reference citations, and other related content are available in the accompanying PDF document. tourism_communication.pdf Abstract With the proposition of rural revitalization and the rise of cultural and tourism industries, the demand for rural image construction and dissemination has increasingly become prominent. Rural cultural squares, as essential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study on the Adoption of Health Information by College Students in Beijing on User-Generated Content Platforms--A Case of Xiaohongshu</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/2023/health-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/2023/health-information/</guid>
      <description>The present article represents a collaborative effort completed by five co-authors, with my contribution focusing specifically on the literature review and data processing sections. The text below encompasses the content of those segments, while the comprehensive full-text version is attached as a PDF file for your reference. ！Download Full Text Abstract This study focuses on the contemporary representative Internet new media platform</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
