<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Wish&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Wish&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wish2333.github.io/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CPlogy-Initial Operation Report</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy-initial-operation-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy-initial-operation-report/</guid>
      <description>Basic Information Platform: Bilibili Key Account Metrics Shift: Followers increased from 285 to 315, Submissions rose from 47 to 48, Total Views surged from 45,000 to 75,000, Likes jumped from 1,400 to 2,000, Coins went up from 696 to 751, Comments expanded from 277 to 405, Favorites climbed from 1,185 to 1,597, Shares marginally grew from 542 to 552. Positioning &amp;amp; Tone Platform Positioning: A comprehensive entertainment and cultural community</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPlogy01-A Candid Critique of BUCCHIGIRI</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy01/</guid>
      <description>大家好呀，我是你们的新人up主wish，今天我们来锐评一下“MAPPA的又一gay佬番”——无人能敌BUCCHIGIRI。是的，我也愿意这么</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Practice Paths for Cultural Square Empowerment in Rural Revitalization Under the Context of Cultural and Tourism Communication--An Investigation Based on Feng Village, a National Key Rural Tourism Site in Guangxi, China</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/tourism-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/tourism-communication/</guid>
      <description>This article is entirely my original work, completed independently on January 10, 2024. Kindly respect the intellectual property rights. The full Chinese text, appendices, reference citations, and other related content are available in the accompanying PDF document. tourism_communication.pdf Abstract With the proposition of rural revitalization and the rise of cultural and tourism industries, the demand for rural image construction and dissemination has increasingly become prominent. Rural cultural squares, as essential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Spatial Inequality within The Dingfuzhuang Community</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/social-spatial-inequality-within-dingfuzhuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/social-spatial-inequality-within-dingfuzhuang/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Through an urban sociological lens, this investigation will delve deeply into the unequal distribution and utilization of social spaces among different areas, neighborhoods, or specific locales within the Dingfuzhuang area of Chaoyang District, Beijing. We aim to identify the concrete manifestations of such inequalities within the particular community, encompassing aspects such as the distribution of infrastructure, allocation of public service facilities, and usage patterns of residential public spaces. Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webclass-AutoCut based on Free Software</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/webclass-autocut-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/webclass-autocut-free/</guid>
      <description>Application Scenarios Online Course Editing: Legacy Courses: Batch update of intros and outros across varied formats (encoding, resolution, frame rate, audio format). New Course Recordings: Processing raw files, focusing on noise reduction, removal of blank segments, and adding standardized intros and outros. Rapid Slicing &amp;amp; Content Review: Based on scripts, for swift editing and review, crucial for content flagged for modification. Requirements Breakdown Legacy Courses: Objective: Replace (delete + add),</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Process of Research in Dingfuzhuang Community</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/the-creative-process-of-dingfuzhuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/the-creative-process-of-dingfuzhuang/</guid>
      <description>理解城市-结课作业 2023-10-28选题：黄淼森 社会空间不平等问题 参考文献 zhihu/p/452072791 zhihu/p/106501422 sohu/a/482049556_121124003 fjyl/file_no=20200910 douban.com/review/14200117/ 选题报告 在报告中，将关注的主题定为“身边的社区存在的社</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study on the Adoption of Health Information by College Students in Beijing on User-Generated Content Platforms--A Case of Xiaohongshu</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/health-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/health-information/</guid>
      <description>The present article represents a collaborative effort completed by five co-authors, with my contribution focusing specifically on the literature review and data processing sections. The text below encompasses the content of those segments, while the comprehensive full-text version is attached as a PDF file for your reference. ！Download Full Text Abstract This study focuses on the contemporary representative Internet new media platform</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cold and Warmth of the Police Station</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2022/the-cold-and-warmth-of-the-police-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2022/the-cold-and-warmth-of-the-police-station/</guid>
      <description>Introduction On March 11th, the documentary Guarding Liberation West 3, co-produced by the Changsha Public Security Bureau and Bilibili, came to a successful conclusion, amassing over 200 million views and sparking heated discussions. Throughout the series, it featured both bizarre incidents that left viewers laughing and crying, as well as thrilling on-site arrests, showcasing both the stern and rigorous law enforcement procedures and heartwarming grassroots services. Behind the hustle and bustle, the guardians never rest; in recent years, documentaries focusing on law enforcement have increasingly attracted the younger generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio Drama Script Based on Kazuha</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2021/radio-drama-script-base-kazuha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2021/radio-drama-script-base-kazuha/</guid>
      <description>Seagulls silent, traveler&amp;rsquo;s sentiment; red leaves aflame, heart of benevolence and righteousness. Setting Disclaimer: This is a derivative creation, all copyrights belong to miHoYo.&#xA;All plot elements are purely fictional and unrelated to any historical figures or nations.&#xA;Introduction In a time of extreme instability across the globe, the General suddenly issued a Sword Hunt Decree, ordering the confiscation of swords carried by civilians, which incited discontent among various samurai factions and civilian organizations, leading them to unite and form a resistance army.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/markdown-syntax-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo | Hugo-stack-theme主题魔改版</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/stack-theme-mod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 1988 03:02:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/stack-theme-mod/</guid>
      <description>Github仓库地址：Mantyke/stack-theme-mod 本主题由CaiJimmy制作并发布，这个仓库是由Mantyke修改的魔改</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
