<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Wish&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Wish&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wish2333.github.io/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>【Conference Paper】Research on the theme evolution of gender and economic public opinion in time series.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/fatcat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/fatcat/</guid>
      <description>The manuscript has been accepted for the 30th AMIC conference. I will be attending and presenting on September 24-26. The link will be provided once the conference proceedings and abstracts are published.&#xA;The official website of the conference&#xA;View the paper (CN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Programming】Web Crawling Practice: Utilizing Open Source Projects to Retrieve Weibo Posts.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/crawler-weibo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/crawler-weibo/</guid>
      <description>https://github.com/dataabc/weiboSpider https://github.com/dataabc/weibo-crawler https://github.com/dataabc/weibo-search Operating Environment Programming Language: Python 3 To install Python, please visit: Python Official Website During the installation process, remember to select &amp;ldquo;Add to PATH&amp;rdquo; Operating Systems: Windows/Linux/macOS weiboSpider Program Installation - Source Code Installation Extract and navigate to the program directory $ pip install -r requirements.txt If encountering errors during the installation of dependencies, please open the requirements.txt file and remove the specified version numbers at the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Academic Research】Empirical Research Design: A Study on the Motivations of Young Adults&#39; Participation in Narrative Creation and Interpretation.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/catmeme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/catmeme/</guid>
      <description>Concept Definition Narrativized Second Creation Short Videos Cultural Remix: Second creation refers to the manner in which internet users, within the online context, utilize the works of others through re-creation to express new viewpoints, giving rise to a form of culture known as &amp;ldquo;remix culture,&amp;rdquo; characterized by the replication, collage, and fusion of elements from different works to create new ones[1]. Second Creation Short Videos: According to the definition provided</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animemory001-The Chronicles of ACGN: The Animated Saga</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/animemory001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/animemory001/</guid>
      <description>View the script (CN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Programming】FFmpeg&#43;Python GUI--Application for the rapid trimming and concatenation of video</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/ffpygui-preversion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/ffpygui-preversion/</guid>
      <description>Github：VideoExtractAndConcat Project Overview This project aims to develop a user-friendly Graphical User Interface (GUI) application for the rapid trimming and concatenation of video intros and outros. Integrating a Qt Designer-built interface with the Python programming language and leveraging the powerful ffmpeg tool, users</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPlogy-Initial Operation Report</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy-initial-operation-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy-initial-operation-report/</guid>
      <description>Basic Information Platform: Bilibili Account: wish_2333 Key Account Metrics Shift: Followers increased from 285 to 315, Submissions rose from 47 to 48, Total Views surged from 45,000 to 75,000, Likes jumped from 1,400 to 2,000, Coins went up from 696 to 751, Comments expanded from 277 to 405, Favorites climbed from 1,185 to 1,597, Shares marginally grew from 542 to 552. Positioning &amp;amp; Tone Platform Positioning: A comprehensive entertainment and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPlogy01-A Candid Critique of BUCCHIGIRI</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy01/</guid>
      <description>View the script (CN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Conference Paper】Exploring the practical path of cultural squares empowering rural revitalization under the background of cultural tourism communication.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/tourism-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/tourism-communication/</guid>
      <description>The manuscript has been accepted for the 30th AMIC conference. I will be attending and presenting on September 24-26. The link will be provided once the conference proceedings and abstracts are published.&#xA;The official website of the conference&#xA;View the full paper (CN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Academic Research】Social Spatial Inequality within The Dingfuzhuang Community</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/social-spatial-inequality-within-dingfuzhuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/social-spatial-inequality-within-dingfuzhuang/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Through an urban sociological lens, this investigation will delve deeply into the unequal distribution and utilization of social spaces among different areas, neighborhoods, or specific locales within the Dingfuzhuang area of Chaoyang District, Beijing. We aim to identify the concrete manifestations of such inequalities within the particular community, encompassing aspects such as the distribution of infrastructure, allocation of public service facilities, and usage patterns of residential public spaces. Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Post-Production】Webclass-AutoCut based on Free Software</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/webclass-autocut-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/webclass-autocut-free/</guid>
      <description>Application Scenarios Online Course Editing: Legacy Courses: Batch update of intros and outros across varied formats (encoding, resolution, frame rate, audio format). New Course Recordings: Processing raw files, focusing on noise reduction, removal of blank segments, and adding standardized intros and outros. Rapid Slicing &amp;amp; Content Review: Based on scripts, for swift editing and review, crucial for content flagged for modification. Requirements Breakdown Legacy Courses: Objective: Replace (delete + add),</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Academic Research】The Process of Research in Dingfuzhuang Community</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/the-creative-process-of-dingfuzhuang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/the-creative-process-of-dingfuzhuang/</guid>
      <description>View the document (CN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Academic Research】A Study on Beijing&#39;s Urban Public Spaces and National Image.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/beijing-public-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/beijing-public-space/</guid>
      <description>Research Background In delving into the realm of urban public spaces, let us commence our exploration from the annals of public space history. Indeed, the term &amp;ldquo;city,&amp;rdquo; employed to delineate vast human settlements geographically, inherently encompasses a pivotal variant of public space—the market, a locus dedicated to commercial transactions. From the Spring and Autumn Period to the Sui and Tang Dynasties, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Academic Research】A Study on the Adoption of Health Information by College Students in Beijing on User-Generated Content Platforms--A Case of Xiaohongshu</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/health-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/health-information/</guid>
      <description>The present article represents a collaborative effort completed by five co-authors, with my contribution focusing specifically on the literature review and data processing sections. The text below encompasses the content of those segments, while the comprehensive full-text version is attached as a PDF file for your reference. View the full paper (CN) Abstract This study focuses on the contemporary representative Internet new media platform Xiaohongshu APP, conducting a survey targeting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cold and Warmth of the Police Station</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2022/the-cold-and-warmth-of-the-police-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2022/the-cold-and-warmth-of-the-police-station/</guid>
      <description>Introduction On March 11th, the documentary Guarding Liberation West 3, co-produced by the Changsha Public Security Bureau and Bilibili, came to a successful conclusion, amassing over 200 million views and sparking heated discussions. Throughout the series, it featured both bizarre incidents that left viewers laughing and crying, as well as thrilling on-site arrests, showcasing both the stern and rigorous law enforcement procedures and heartwarming grassroots services. Behind the hustle and bustle, the guardians never rest; in recent years, documentaries focusing on law enforcement have increasingly attracted the younger generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio Drama Script Based on Kazuha</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2021/radio-drama-script-base-kazuha/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2021/radio-drama-script-base-kazuha/</guid>
      <description>Seagulls silent, traveler&amp;rsquo;s sentiment; red leaves aflame, heart of benevolence and righteousness. Setting Disclaimer: This is a derivative creation, all copyrights belong to miHoYo.&#xA;All plot elements are purely fictional and unrelated to any historical figures or nations.&#xA;Introduction In a time of extreme instability across the globe, the General suddenly issued a Sword Hunt Decree, ordering the confiscation of swords carried by civilians, which incited discontent among various samurai factions and civilian organizations, leading them to unite and form a resistance army.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/markdown-syntax-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 1988 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo | Hugo-stack-theme主题魔改版</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/stack-theme-mod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 1988 03:02:52 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/1988/stack-theme-mod/</guid>
      <description>Github仓库地址：Mantyke/stack-theme-mod 本主题由CaiJimmy制作并发布，这个仓库是由Mantyke修改的魔改</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
