<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Media Literacy on Wish&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/tags/media-literacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Media Literacy on Wish&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wish2333.github.io/en/tags/media-literacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>【Conference Paper】Research on the theme evolution of gender and economic public opinion in time series.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/fatcat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/fatcat/</guid>
      <description>The manuscript has been accepted for the 30th AMIC conference. I will be attending and presenting on September 24-26. The link will be provided once the conference proceedings and abstracts are published.&#xA;The official website of the conference&#xA;View the paper (CN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Academic Research】Empirical Research Design: A Study on the Motivations of Young Adults&#39; Participation in Narrative Creation and Interpretation.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/catmeme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/catmeme/</guid>
      <description>Concept Definition Narrativized Second Creation Short Videos Cultural Remix: Second creation refers to the manner in which internet users, within the online context, utilize the works of others through re-creation to express new viewpoints, giving rise to a form of culture known as &amp;ldquo;remix culture,&amp;rdquo; characterized by the replication, collage, and fusion of elements from different works to create new ones[1]. Second Creation Short Videos: According to the definition provided</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPlogy-Initial Operation Report</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy-initial-operation-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/cplogy-initial-operation-report/</guid>
      <description>Basic Information Platform: Bilibili Account: wish_2333 Key Account Metrics Shift: Followers increased from 285 to 315, Submissions rose from 47 to 48, Total Views surged from 45,000 to 75,000, Likes jumped from 1,400 to 2,000, Coins went up from 696 to 751, Comments expanded from 277 to 405, Favorites climbed from 1,185 to 1,597, Shares marginally grew from 542 to 552. Positioning &amp;amp; Tone Platform Positioning: A comprehensive entertainment and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Conference Paper】Exploring the practical path of cultural squares empowering rural revitalization under the background of cultural tourism communication.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/tourism-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2024/tourism-communication/</guid>
      <description>The manuscript has been accepted for the 30th AMIC conference. I will be attending and presenting on September 24-26. The link will be provided once the conference proceedings and abstracts are published.&#xA;The official website of the conference&#xA;View the full paper (CN)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Academic Research】A Study on Beijing&#39;s Urban Public Spaces and National Image.</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/beijing-public-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/beijing-public-space/</guid>
      <description>Research Background In delving into the realm of urban public spaces, let us commence our exploration from the annals of public space history. Indeed, the term &amp;ldquo;city,&amp;rdquo; employed to delineate vast human settlements geographically, inherently encompasses a pivotal variant of public space—the market, a locus dedicated to commercial transactions. From the Spring and Autumn Period to the Sui and Tang Dynasties, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Academic Research】A Study on the Adoption of Health Information by College Students in Beijing on User-Generated Content Platforms--A Case of Xiaohongshu</title>
      <link>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/health-information/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wish2333.github.io/en/2023/health-information/</guid>
      <description>The present article represents a collaborative effort completed by five co-authors, with my contribution focusing specifically on the literature review and data processing sections. The text below encompasses the content of those segments, while the comprehensive full-text version is attached as a PDF file for your reference. View the full paper (CN) Abstract This study focuses on the contemporary representative Internet new media platform Xiaohongshu APP, conducting a survey targeting</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
